ALL THE TAXES,
DOES IT AFFECT
THEIR TAXES?
IT WILL.
IT'LL SHOW US
ITS OWN LINE
ITEM NOW.
OK.
YEAH.
SO IT'S EASY
MATH TO FIGURE
OUT WHAT IT'S
GOING TO BE.
YOU JUST LOOK
AT THE TAX
BILL.
RIGHT.
AND IT'LL BE
BROKEN DOWN LAND
AND HOUSE SEPARATE.
RIGHT.
YOU TAKE THE
PART THEY CHARGE
YOU FOR THE
HOUSE, HOW MUCH
THEY'RE CHARGING PER
SQUARE FOOT OF
THE HOUSE, AND
JUST DO THE
MATH AND SAY,
OK, IT'S A
900 SQUARE FEET.
AGAIN, THIS IS
A MADE UP
NUMBER.
THEY CHARGE IN
$5,000 A YEAR.
SO IT COMES
UP TO $3
A SQUARE FOOT.
AND THEN YOU
JUST SAY, OK,
I'M BUILDING 900
SQUARE FOOT ADU
TIMES 300.
THAT'S WHAT I'M
GOING TO PAY
IN TAXES.
OK.
$3.
EXCUSE ME.
IT'S EASY MATH.
ONCE I PULL
THE TAX BILL,
I CAN DO
THE MATH FOR
YOU.
RIGHT.
JUST FOR ELECTRICITY
AND ALL THAT.
SEPARATE.
RIGHT.
THE ONLY THING
IS, IF I
COUNTED DOWN, IT
DOES CHARGE FOR
SEWER AND WATER.
SO WE'D HAVE
TO JUST WORK
SOMETHING OUT.
WELL, WE CAN
DO A PRIVATE
WATER METER INSIDE
THE ADU IF
YOU'D LIKE.
OH, WE'RE TRYING
TO FIGURE OUT.
SO YOU CAN
DO THE MATH
YOURSELF.
OK.